<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="110">
    <title>
        <en>Dispo List</en>
        <de>Dispositionsliste</de>
        <fr>Liste De Disposition</fr>
        <it>Lista Di Disposizione</it>
        <pt>Lista De Disposição</pt>
        <es>Lista De Disposición</es>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[DispoList - Stock overview and best prices per product. Includes filter system with zones and stations.
Credits: HappyLooser (HL HUD System), FedAction (NF Marsch map & inspiration).
MP: Each player needs the mod. Not tested in multiplayer — use at your own risk.

Changelog (1.2.6.x): Construction site demand (EverythingConstructable, if installed) is now automatically deducted from the free amount. Toggle directly in the main HUD by clicking the free-amount explanation line. g_farmCore export extended.
]]></en>
        <de><![CDATA[DispoList - Lagerbestand und Bestpreise pro Ware. Mit Filtersystem nach Bereichen und Stationen.
Credits: HappyLooser (HL HUD System), FedAction (NF Marsch Karte & Inspiration).
MP: Jeder Spieler benötigt den Mod. Nicht im Multiplayer getestet — auf eigene Gefahr.

Changelog (1.2.6.x): Baustellen-Bedarf (EverythingConstructable, falls installiert) wird jetzt automatisch von der freien Menge abgezogen. Umschalten direkt im Haupt-HUD per Klick auf die Frei-Erklärung. g_farmCore-Export erweitert.
]]></de>
        <fr><![CDATA[DispoList - Aperçu des stocks et meilleurs prix par produit. Système de filtres par zones et stations.
Crédits: HappyLooser (HL HUD System), FedAction (carte NF Marsch & inspiration).
MP: Chaque joueur a besoin du mod. Non testé en multijoueur — à utiliser à vos risques.
]]></fr>
        <it><![CDATA[DispoList - Panoramica delle scorte e prezzi migliori per prodotto. Sistema di filtri per zone e stazioni.
Crediti: HappyLooser (HL HUD System), FedAction (mappa NF Marsch & ispirazione).
MP: Ogni giocatore ha bisogno del mod. Non testato in multiplayer — usare a proprio rischio.
]]></it>
        <pt><![CDATA[DispoList - Visão geral do estoque e melhores preços por produto. Sistema de filtros por zonas e estações.
Créditos: HappyLooser (HL HUD System), FedAction (mapa NF Marsch & inspiração).
MP: Cada jogador precisa do mod. Não testado em multijogador — use por sua conta e risco.
]]></pt>
        <es><![CDATA[DispoList - Resumen de existencias y mejores precios por producto. Sistema de filtros por zonas y estaciones.
Créditos: HappyLooser (HL HUD System), FedAction (mapa NF Marsch & inspiración).
MP: Cada jugador necesita el mod. No probado en multijugador — úselo bajo su propio riesgo.
]]></es>
    </description>
    <author>LazyChilla</author>
    <version>1.2.6.3</version>
    <iconFilename>icon_dispoList.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="hlUtils/_hlUtils.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="hlHudSystem/hlHudSystem.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="scripte_dl/xml/DL_Display_XmlBox.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="scripte_dl/draw/DL_Display_DrawBox.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="dispoList.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>

    <actions>
        <action name="HL_ONOFFMOUSECURSOR" ignoreComboMask="false" axisType="HALF" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE" />
        <action name="DL_ONOFFDISPLAY" ignoreComboMask="false" axisType="HALF" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE"/>
    </actions>

    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="HL_ONOFFMOUSECURSOR">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_f9" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="DL_ONOFFDISPLAY">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lshift KEY_c" axisComponent="+" neutralInput="0" index="1"/>
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>

    <l10n>
        <text name="input_HL_ONOFFMOUSECURSOR">
            <en>Toggle Mouse Cursor (HL HUD System)</en>
            <de>Mauszeiger ein/aus (HL HUD System)</de>
            <fr>Curseur souris on/off (HL HUD System)</fr>
            <it>Cursore mouse on/off (HL HUD System)</it>
            <pt>Cursor do rato on/off (HL HUD System)</pt>
            <es>Cursor ratón on/off (HL HUD System)</es>
        </text>
        <text name="input_DL_ONOFFDISPLAY">
            <en>Toggle Dispo List</en>
            <de>Dispositionsliste ein/aus</de>
            <fr>Afficher/masquer DispoList</fr>
            <it>Mostra/nascondi DispoList</it>
            <pt>Mostrar/ocultar DispoList</pt>
            <es>Mostrar/ocultar DispoList</es>
        </text>
    </l10n>
</modDesc>
